<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Spy</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>

    <string name="min">min</string>
    <string name="players">Players</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="player">Player</string>
    <string name="spies">Spies</string>
    <string name="timer">Timer</string>
    <string name="set">Set</string>
    <string name="click_to_see_you_role">Click to see your role</string>
    <string name="you_member">You are a local. All players except a spy know this location. Ask your friends different questions to figure out which one of them is a spy</string>
    <string name="you_spy_hint">Try to figure out what location the locals are talking about</string>
    <string name="you_spy">You are a spy</string>
    <string name="hint_timer">Start asking questions! Find a Spy before the time runs out, otherwise he will win</string>
    <string name="was_spy">A Spy was</string>
    <string name="were_spies">The Spies were</string>
    <string name="restart">Once more</string>
    <string name="choose">Choose a set</string>
    <string name="print_word">Enter a location</string>
    <string name="add_word">Add a word</string>
    <string name="add_set">Add a set</string>
    <string name="toast_empty_set">You cannot select an empty set</string>
    <string name="new_set">New set</string>

    <string name="first_page_title">How about playing Spy?</string>
    <string name="first_page_text">Swipe and we will tell you what to do</string>

    <string name="second_page_title">Roles</string>
    <string name="second_page_text">In the game, you are either a local or a Spy. Only locals know the location and they must find the Spy, while the spy must guess the game location</string>

    <string name="third_page_title">Ask questions</string>
    <string name="third_page_text">You can ask questions about the game location.
The responding player will be the next to ask the question.
The player who was a Spy in the last game  is the first to ask a question</string>

    <string name="fourth_page_title">Listen</string>
    <string name="fourth_page_text">Listen carefully to the answers and questions of other players.
Remember, the Spy does not know the location, which is why he may
act incorrectly</string>

    <string name="fifth_page_title">Vote</string>
    <string name="fifth_page_text">Say: “I found the Spy” and say his/her Name. After that a vote is taken.
All players vote on whether the named player is a Spy
</string>

    <string name="sixth_page_title">Victory?</string>
    <string name="sixth_page_text">If all players agree, the player selected by the vote shows his card. If he turns out to be a local, then the Spy wins. If this person is really a Spy, the locals win.
If not all players agree, then the game continues. If the Spy guessed about the discussed location, then he can name it.
If the Spy guessed it, then he wins. Otherwise, he will be defeated.</string>

    <string name="seventh_page_title">Timer</string>
    <string name="seventh_page_text">Don`t forget about the time. It`s limited, so hurry up.
When the time is up, the Spy wins</string>


    <string name="guide_first_title">So, let`s start?</string>
    <string name="guide_first_text">First, select the conditions of the game: a set of words, the time of the game,
the number of players and spies and the game language.
</string>

    <string name="guide_second_title">So how to play?</string>
    <string name="guide_second_text">There are two roles in the game: a local and a spy. For everyone to know their roles,
pass the phone to each player in turn.
</string>

    <string name="guide_third_title">Won’t the other players see my role?</string>
    <string name="guide_third_text">When you click on the card, it will turn over. On the reverse side,
you will either find out the location, or be glad to know that you are the Spy.
After another click, your card will hide and you will see the cover of the next card.
Then pass the phone to the next player, so that he turned over his card.
When everyone knows their roles, start the game. Ask each other questions about the place that was on the cards of the locals, for example: “What color is this place?”,
“How often do you go there?”, “Do you want to return to this place?”.
The main task of the locals is to find the Spy (or Spies), he has no idea what place you are talking about.
The Spy`s job is to pretend he is local and knows the game location.
He has to try to guess what location the players are at.
</string>

    <string name="guide_fourth_title">What if you guess who the Spy is?</string>
    <string name="guide_fourth_text">Say: “I found the Spy” and say his/her Name. After that a vote is taken.
All players vote on whether the named player is a Spy.
If all players agree, the player selected by the vote shows his card. If he turns out to be a local, then the Spy wins.
If this person is really a Spy, the locals win.
If not all players agree, then the game continues.
You can also play without voting, instead, all players on the count of 3 must point to the player who, in their opinion, is a Spy.
Если все выбрали одного и того же игрока, то он должен раскрыть свою роль.Если я Шпион и догадался локацию, что мне делать? Просто скажи: “Я
знаю локацию” и назви её. Если ты угадаешь, то выиграешь. Ошибаешься -
выиграют местные
</string>

    <string name="guide_fifth_title">Why you need a timer</string>
    <string name="guide_fifth_text">If the locals managed to expose the Spy before he sounded
timer, then they will win. If the Spy could last all this time -
he wins.
</string>

    <string name="guide_sixth_title">How do I play Multi-Spy Mode? </string>
    <string name="guide_sixth_text">The number of Spies should always be less than the number
local. Each Spy plays for himself, because only one wins.
To win, the locals must now expose all the spies. If a
since they do not expose everyone, then it is precisely those Spies who are not
exposed. In the case when all players vote against the person who
Consider a Spy: if he turns out to be local, the Spies win.
If the locals guess right, the exposed Spy leaves the game, and
the game itself continues, because you need to figure out all the spies. When
when one of the Spies calls the location: If he guesses, the game
ends and this Spy wins. If he calls the wrong
place - the game continues without him. Cards fall out completely
by chance, so your role only depends on your luck!
</string>


    <string name="find">Find out who the spy is</string>



    <string name="eng">English</string>
    <string name="rus">Русский</string>
    <string name="ukr">Українська</string>
    <string name="changed_lang">Language changed successfully</string>

    <string name="countries">Countries</string>
    <string-array name="countries">
        <item>Ukraine</item>
        <item>USA</item>
        <item>Germany</item>
        <item>Spain</item>
        <item>Portugal</item>
        <item>Italy</item>
        <item>France</item>
        <item>Netherlands</item>
        <item>United Kingdom</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>North Korea</item>
        <item>Japan</item>
        <item>Brazil</item>
        <item>Mexico</item>
        <item>Poland</item>
        <item>Hungary</item>
        <item>Belarus</item>
        <item>Turkey</item>
        <item>India</item>
        <item>Australia</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="basic">Basic</string>
    <string-array name="basic">
        <item> Residential building </item>
        <item> Supermarket </item>
        <item> Auto parts market </item>
        <item> Food Market </item>
        <item> Ice Arena </item>
        <item> Bunker </item>
        <item> Landfill </item>
        <item> Garage </item>
        <item> Country house </item>
        <item> Palace </item>
        <item> Church </item>
        <item> Cemetery </item>
        <item> Coffin </item>
        <item> Elevator </item>
        <item> Subway Escalator </item>
        <item> Park </item>
        <item> Casino </item>
        <item> Bank </item>
        <item> Military Hospital </item>
        <item> Film Studio </item>
        <item> Ocean Liner </item>
        <item> Vegetable base </item>
        <item> School </item>
        <item> Kindergarten </item>
        <item> Hotel </item>
        <item> Gas station (refueling) </item>
        <item> Car wash </item>
        <item> Bar </item>
        <item> Hardware store </item>
        <item> Service station </item>
        <item> Tire service </item>
        <item> Space Station </item>
        <item> Moon </item>
        <item> Mars </item>
        <item> Restaurant </item>
        <item> Submarine </item>
        <item> Beach </item>
        <item> Desert </item>
        <item> Party </item>
        <item> Embassy </item>
        <item> Aircraft </item>
        <item> Helicopter </item>
        <item> Amphitheater </item>
        <item> Hairdresser </item>
        <item> Pharmacy </item>
        <item> Library </item>
        <item> Gym </item>
        <item> Swimming pool </item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="transport">Transport</string>
    <string-array name="transport">
        <item> Tram </item>
        <item> Trolleybus </item>
        <item> Bus </item>
        <item> Passenger car </item>
        <item> Truck </item>
        <item> Truck </item>
        <item> Metro </item>
        <item> Tractor "Belarus" </item>
        <item> Bulldozer </item>
        <item> Excavator </item>
        <item> Crane </item>
        <item> Garbage Truck </item>
        <item> Carriage </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>